TRAN

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

INTRODUCTION

I am Tran Thanh Thai, a full-stack developer in Spring framework and ReactJS, with good knowledge of java, OOP, Database, Algorithm & Data Structure.

When I was a high school student in a Mathematics class, I spent 3 years learning this subject deeply. Therefore, I am very confident in my logical thinking, critical thinking, and self-study as well.

Last but not least, I am willing to approach new technologies in a positive way. I am looking forward to supporting and learning from my teammates.





Male



07741712





ttran07@gmail.com



facebook.com/vincent



Nguyen Duy Trinh, Thu Duc

EDUCATION

Univesity of Medicine and Phamarcy at Ho Chi Minh City 09/2016 - 12/2019

Pharmceutical

STUDY RESERVATION

► Funix Center (A member of FPT Corporation)

10/2020 - Now

Software engineering

Complete 3 certificates:

- Basics of programming (HTML, CSS, Javascript)
- Mobile application development (Java, Algorithm & Data Structure)
- Web application development (Servlet, JSP, JDBC, Spring framework, Design Database & SQL)

OBJECTIVES

- From 3 to 6 months

 Become a junior developer
- From 2 to 4 years
 Become a senior developer, get AWS certification
- After 4 years
 Technical Lead

SKILLS

Programming Languages

EXPERIENCE

► thuocsi company

05/2019 - 08/2019

Internship

- Customer Service
- Give my opinions and report problems about the website to the manager.

▶ Funix

03/2021 - Now

Tutor

- Help mentors to support the other students on the Slack application.
- Give my opinions about the curriculum.

ACTIVITIES

► Tue Duc charity fund

06/2019 - Now

Volunteering

- 1. Community activities:
- · Awarding scholarship to studious students.
- Donating gifts (money, clothes, nourishment) to the poor.
- · Organizing indoor/outdoor activities for children.
- Teaching children life skills/ lessons (honesty, responsibility, forgiveness, compassion, respect, good manners, etc.).
- · Constructing roads and bridges.
- 2. Religion activities:
- Setting free (animals caught).
- Doing volunteer work/ praying at the temple.
- Handing out the cause and effect pictures.
- 3. Environmental activities:
- Afforestation.
- The the local living/ park clean up.

- Front-end: HTML/CSS, Javascript
- Back-end: Java
- Database: SQL Server, MySQL
- Framework: Spring MVC, ReactJS
- Algorithm and Data structure: Types of sorting, LinkedList, Queue, Stack,
 Binary Tree

Language

English - B1 (Intermediate)
Vietnamese (native speaker)

GITHUB & PROJECT

https://github.com/thaitechnet

Project 1: eCommerce Website: Servlet, JSP, MySQL, JDBC

https://github.com/thaitechnet/ecommercejsp-servlet

Project 2: eCommerce Website: Spring MVC, MySQL, JDBC, XAMPP

https://github.com/thaitechnet/PameShoesS hop-eCommerce-Website-Spring-MCV